A Guide to the Policy Office Legislative Files of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
- HB 734 (98) George Ward Dalton Bridge (Box 8, Folder 30)
- HB 735 (98) Motor Vehicle Speed Detection Devices (Box 8, Folder 31)
- HB 738 (98) Commercial Vehicle Parking in Residential Areas (Box 8, Folder 32)
- HB 740 (98) Redevelopment Projects; Spot Blight Abatement (Box 8, Folder 33)
- HB 742 (98) Public Defender Offices (Box 8, Folder 34)
- HB 755 (98) Public Utilities; Certificate of Convenience and Necessity (Box 8, Folder 35)
- HB 756 (98) Gambling; Help for Compulsive Gamblers (Box 8, Folder 36)
- HB 757 (98) Concealed Weapons (Box 8, Folder 37)
- HB 761 (98) Wills and Descendant's Estates; Augmented Estate (Box 8, Folder 38)
- HB 764 (98) Housing; Spot Blight Abatement (Box 8, Folder 39)
- HB 768 (98) Ineligibility for Concealed Handgun Permit (Box 8, Folder 40)
- HB 769 (98) Pawnbrokers; Licensure (Box 8, Folder 41)
- HB 770 (98) Special License Plates; Supporters of the AAA (Box 8, Folder 42)
- HB 777 (98) Service of Process on Foreign Defendants (Box 8, Folder 43)
- HB 779 (98) Property Conveyance; Lands in James River (Box 8, Folder 44)
- HB 780 (98) Adult Care Residences (Box 8, Folder 45)
- HB 781 (98) Health Insurance Portability Act; Conformity (Box 8, Folder 46)
- HB 782 (98) Health Insurance; Guaranteed Availability, Preexisting Conditions (Box 8, Folder 47)
- HB 783 (98) Service of Civil Papers by Town Police Officers (Box 8, Folder 48)
- HB 785 (98) Sale of Certain Property Acquired by Power of Eminent Domain (Box 8, Folder 49)
- HB 790 (98) Remote Access; Public Records (Box 8, Folder 50)
- HB 791 (98) Lien for Medical Services (Box 8, Folder 51)
- HB 792 (98) Remote Access to Certain Records (Box 8, Folder 52)
- HB 793 (98) Deeds; Requirement for Indexing (Box 8, Folder 53)
- HB 794 (98) Electronic Filing of Documents; Sunset (Box 8, Folder 54)
- HB 798 (98) Edinburg Town Charts (Box 8, Folder 55)
- HB 799 (98) Special License Plates; Persons Once Declared MIA (Box 8, Folder 56)
- HB 802 (98) Addresses of Trustees in Deeds of Trust (Box 8, Folder 57)
- HB 803 (98) Child Protective Services; Infant Dependent on Controlled Sub. (Box 8, Folder 58)
- HB 804 (98) Health Insurance for State Employees; Managed Care Options (Box 8, Folder 59)
- HB 807 (98) Clean Water Farm Award Program (Box 8, Folder 60)
- HB 808 (98) Number of Deputies (Box 8, Folder 61)
- HB 809 (98) Board for Contractors; Unlicensed Activity (Box 8, Folder 62)
- HB 812 (98) Workers' Compensation; Payments to Infants or Incapac. Persons (Box 8, Folder 63)
- HB 813 (98) Workers' Compensation; Receipt of Notice on Awards, Rehearing (Box 8, Folder 64)
- HB 815 (98) Preservation Easement Fund (Box 8, Folder 65)
- HB 816 (98) Regulation of Water Transport of Wastes (Box 8, Folder 66)
- HB 817 (98) Personal Watercraft; Ordinance Enforcement (Box 8, Folder 67)
- HB 820 (98) Instruction of Blind and Visually Impaired Students (Box 8, Folder 68)
- HB 821 (98) Property Conveyance; Fort Boykin State Park (Box 8, Folder 69)
- HB 822 (98) State Librarian (Box 8, Folder 70)
- HB 825 (98) Business-Education Partnership Program; Members, Terms (Box 8, Folder 71)
- HB 826 (98) Purple Heart Trail (Box 8, Folder 72)
- HB 827 (98) Roanoke Higher Education Authority; Membership (Box 8, Folder 73)
- HB 830 (98) Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Notice to Tenants (Box 8, Folder 74)
- HB 834 (98) Property Owners' Association Act; Special Assessments (Box 8, Folder 75)
- HB 835 (98) Escheators' Bonding Requirements (Box 8, Folder 76)
- HB 836 (98) Jurisdiction of Corporate Authorities (Box 8, Folder 77)
- HB 837 (98) Assignment of Lottery Proceeds (Box 8, Folder 78)
- HB 838 (98) Purchase of Handguns by Fire Marshall (Box 8, Folder 79)
- HB 843 (98) Do Not Resuscitate Orders (Box 8, Folder 80)
- HB 845 (98) Memorials for War Veterans (Box 8, Folder 81)
- HB 848 (98) Earned-Income Tax Credit (Box 8, Folder 82)
- HB 849 (98) Workforce Training at Community Colleges (Box 8, Folder 83)
- HB 850 (98) Procurement Act; Participation in Public Contracts (Box 8, Folder 84)
- HB 851 (98) Workforce Training Council, Statewide (Box 8, Folder 85)
- HB 852 (98) Subdivision of a Lot for Conveyance to a Family Member (Box 8, Folder 86)
- HB 854 (98) Health Insurance; Small Employer Market (Box 8, Folder 87)
- HB 855 (98) Life and Health Insurance Policies; Delivery Requirements (Box 8, Folder 88)
- HB 857 (98) Practice of Surgery (Box 8, Folder 89)
- HB 858 (98) Visually Handicapped (Box 8, Folder 90)
- HB 859 (98) Criminal History Record Check for Private School Employees (Box 8, Folder 91)
- HB 861 (98) End-of-Life Decisions (Box 8, Folder 92)
- HB 865 (98) Regulation of Private Security Services (Box 8, Folder 93)
- HB 867 (98) Driver's Licenses; Learner's Permits for Motorcycles, Etc. (Box 8, Folder 94)
- HB 868 (98) Special License Plates; Wildlife Foundation and Federation of Virginia (Box 8, Folder 95)
- HB 872 (98) Driver Demerit Points (Box 8, Folder 96)
- HB 875 (98) Admissions Tax in Nelson County (Box 8, Folder 97)
- HB 877 (98) Registration-Exempt Vehicles for Farm Produce and Livestock (Box 8, Folder 98)
- HB 878 (98) Workers' Compensation; To Provide Copies of Medical Reports (Box 8, Folder 99)
- HB 879 (98) Property Conveyance; Property Held by VPI and SU (Box 8, Folder 100)
- HB 883 (98) Motor Vehicle Insurance; Cancellations and Non-renewal (Box 8, Folder 101)
- HB 884 (98) Insurance; Written or Oral Notification of Cancellation of Policy (Box 8, Folder 102)
- HB 888 (98) Payments for Children from Other Areas in Secure Detention Facilities (Box 8, Folder 103)
- HB 889 (98) Boundary Line Between Loudoun Co., VA and Jefferson Co., WV (Box 8, Folder 104)
- HB 893 (98) Suspension of Students from School Attendance (Box 8, Folder 105)
- HB 896 (98) Driver Education Programs (Box 8, Folder 106)
- HB 897 (98) Assessments for Local Road Improvements (Box 8, Folder 107)
- HB 899 (98) Fire Protection; Appointment of Assistant Fire Marshalls (Box 8, Folder 108)
- HB 902 (98) Elections; Town of South Boston (Box 9, Folder 1)
- HB 903 (98) Definition of No Wake (Box 9, Folder 2)
- HB 904 (98) Boating; No Wake Speed (Box 9, Folder 3)
- HB 905 (98) Personal Watercraft Rentals (Box 9, Folder 4)
- HB 906 (98) Limited Liability Company Act (Box 9, Folder 5)
- HB 909 (98) Workers' Compensation Notice (Box 9, Folder 6)
- HB 912 (98) Gray and Rain Water Use Guidelines (Box 9, Folder 7)
- HB 914 (98) Teacher Evaluation (Box 9, Folder 8)
- HB 915 (98) Health Insurance for State Employees; Prostate (Box 8, Folder 9)
- HB 916 (98) Hearing Impairment Identification and Monitoring System (Box 9, Folder 10)
- HB 917 (98) Undergraduate and Vocational Incentive Scholarship Program (Box 9, Folder 11)
- HB 918 (98) Literary Fund Loans (Box 9, Folder 12)
- HB 924 (98) Comprehensive Services Act (Box 9, Folder 13)
- HB 924 (98) Comprehensive Services Act (Box 9, Folder 13)
- HB 925 (98) Highway and Transportation Rights-of-Way (Box 9, Folder 14)
- HB 927 (98) Child Care Regulations (Box 9, Folder 15)
- HB 928 (98) Board for Contractors; Definitions; Exemptions; Class C License (Box 9, Folder 16)
- HB 930 (98) Interior Designers (Box 9, Folder 17)
- HB 935 (98) Uniform Statewide Building Code; Definitions (Box 9, Folder 18)
- HB 938 (98) Labor; Migrant Workers (Box 9, Folder 19)
- HB 939 (98) Alcoholic Beverage Control; Licenses (Box 9, Folder 20)
- HB 940 (98) Juveniles; Mental Health Screening (Box 9, Folder 21)
- HB 941 (98) Assistive Technology Device Warranties Act (Box 9, Folder 22)
- HB 943 (98) County Administrator to Maintain Centralized System of Accounting (Box 9, Folder 23)
- HB 945 (98) Mixed Beverage Club Event Licenses (Box 9, Folder 24)
- HB 946 (98) Child Care; Proof of Identity (Box 9, Folder 25)
- HB 948 (98) Compensation of Court-Appointed Counsel (Box 9, Folder 26)
- HB 949 (98) Funding for Deputy Sheriffs (Box 9, Folder 27)
- HB 950 (98) Authority to Cut Grass; Henry County (Box 9, Folder 28)
- HB 952 (98) Capias or Warrant; Arrest Outside Locality Where Charged/Tried (Box 9, Folder 29)
- HB 953 (98) Suspension of Driver's Licenses (Box 9, Folder 30)
- HB 957 (98) Public Rights-of-Way; Telecommunication Facilities (Box 9, Folder 31)
- HB 958 (98) Mass Transit; Local Aid (Box 9, Folder 32)
- HB 961 (98) Revision of Civil Verdict (Box 9, Folder 33)
- HB 963 (98) Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission (Box 9, Folder 34)
- HB 964 (98) Judicial Inquiry and Review Commission (Box 9, Folder 35)
- HB 967 (98) ABC; Illegal Acts by Employees of Licensees (Box 9, Folder 36)
- HB 968 (98) Home Instruction (Box 9, Folder 37)
- HB 972 (98) Concrete Plant Water Discharge General Permits (Box 9, Folder 38)
- HB 973 (98) Real Estate Broker and Salespersons; Provisions (Box 9, Folder 39)
- HB 976 (98) Property Conveyance; Natural Tunnel State Park (Box 9, Folder 40)
- HB 977 (98) Coalfield Educational Empowerment Program (Box 9, Folder 41)
- HB 978 (98) Mine Reclamation Performance Bonds (Box 9, Folder 42)
- HB 984 (98) Enterprise Zones; Redesignation (Box 9, Folder 43)
- HB 990 (98) Medical Assistance Services; Children and Young Adults, Special Needs (Box 9, Folder 44)
- HB 991 (98) Confined Animal Feeding Operations (Box 9, Folder 45)
- HB 992 (98) Oyster Inspection Tax (Box 9, Folder 46)
- HB 993 (98) MRC; Sale of Gear Licenses and Permits (Box 9, Folder 47)
- HB 994 (98) Real Estate Board; Exemptions from License (Box 9, Folder 48)
- HB 995 (98) Special License Plates; Eastern Shore Tourism (Box 9, Folder 49)
- HB 1001 (98) Campaign Finance Disclosure; Reports of Pre-Election Contributions (Box 9, Folder 50)
- HB 1003 (98) Tort Claims Act; Inmate Claims (Box 9, Folder 51)
- HB 1009 (98) Procurement of Computer Equipment (Box 9, Folder 52)
- HB 1010 (98) Cooperation with a Law-Enforcement Officer (Box 9, Folder 53)
- HB 1013 (98) Motor Vehicle, T and M Vehicle, Trailer, and Motorcycle Dealers (Box 9, Folder 54)
- HB 1014 (98) Restricted Driver's Licenses (Box 9, Folder 55)
- HB 1016 (98) Officers of Election; Hours of Service (Box 9, Folder 56)
- HB 1019 (98) Local Assessments for Relocation of Utility Lines (Box 9, Folder 57)
- HB 1021 (98) Medical Assistance Services (Box 9, Folder 58)
- HB 1023 (98) Volunteer Dentists and Dental Hygienists (Box 9, Folder 59)
- HB 1027 (98) Operation of Personal Watercraft; Penalty (Box 9, Folder 60)
- HB 1028 (98) Winegrowers Advisory Board; Members (Box 9, Folder 61)
- HB 1030 (98) Buses (Box 9, Folder 62)
- HB 1031 (98) Terms of School Board Members for City of Williamsburg (Box 9, Folder 63)
- HB 1038 (98) Driver Improvement Clinic Fees (Box 9, Folder 64)
- HB 1040 (98) Number of Deputies (Box 9, Folder 65)
- HB 1041 (98) Costs of Maintenance of Juveniles (Box 9, Folder 66)
- HB 1042 (98) Local Water Supply Systems (Box 9, Folder 67)
- HB 1045 (98) Criminal Procurement; Payment by Credit Card (Box 9, Folder 68)
- HB 1047 (98) Increasing School Board Salaries (Box 9, Folder 69)
- HB 1048 (98) T. George Vaughan, Jr., Memorial Highway (Box 9, Folder 70)
- HB 1054 (98) Child Support (Box 9, Folder 71)
- HB 1055 (98) Health Professions; Nursing (Box 9, Folder 72)
- HB 1060 (98) School Nurse Incentive Grants Program and Fund (Box 9, Folder 73)
- HB 1064 (98) Curfew Violations (Box 9, Folder 74)
- HB 1066 (98) Workers' Compensation; Burial Expenses (Box 9, Folder 75)
- HB 1067 (98) Child Protective Services; Custody (Box 9, Folder 76)
- HB 1073 (98) Election Law; Contested Elections for General Assembly (Box 9, Folder 77)
- HB 1074 (98) Children's Medical Security Insurance Plan (Box 9, Folder 78)
- HB 1075 (98) HMO; Point-of-Service Plans (Box 9, Folder 79)
- HB 1077 (98) Cemetery Board (Box 9, Folder 80)
- HB 1078 (98) Board of Funeral Directors and Embalmers; Cremation (Box 9, Folder 81)
- HB 1079 (98) Open Video Systems (Box 9, Folder 82)
- HB 1080 (98) Juvenile Community Crime Control Act (Box 9, Folder 83)
- HB 1081 (98) Placement of Juveniles (Box 9, Folder 84)
- HB 1082 (98) Employee Relations Counselors; State Grievance Procedure (Box 9, Folder 85)
- HB 1083 (98) Abandoned Vehicles; Liens (Box 9, Folder 86)
- HB 1084 (98) Medical Assistance Services (Box 9, Folder 87)
- HB 1085 (98) Medical Assistance Services (Box 9, Folder 88)
- HB 1091 (98) Disabled Hunters; Use of Crossbows (Box 9, Folder 89)
- HB 1094 (98) Constitutional Amendment; Qualification of Voter, Overseas Employees (Box 9, Folder 90)
- HB 1100 (98) Refuse Collection and Disposal; Fees (Box 9, Folder 91)
- HB 1101 (98) Prescription Dispensing Record Disclosure (Box 9, Folder 92)
- HB 1102 (98) Optometrists; Controlled Substances (Box 9, Folder 93)
- HB 1103 (98) Low Income Home Energy Assistance (Box 9, Folder 94)
- HB 1104 (98) Information Regarding Certain Offenses Committed by Students (Box 9, Folder 95)
- HB 1105 (98) Real Estate Time-Share Act (Box 9, Folder 96)
- HB 1106 (98) Habeas Corpus (Box 9, Folder 97)
- HB 1108 (98) Aviation Board; Grants (Box 9, Folder 98)
- HB 1110 (98) Prescribed Burn Managers Program (Box 9, Folder 99)
- HB 1111 (98) Certification of School Employees in CPR (Box 9, Folder 100)
- HB 1112 (98) Highway Improvements by Counties (Box 9, Folder 101)
- HB 1113 (98) Civil Immunity; Ski Patrol Emergency Assistance (Box 9, Folder 102)
- HB 1114 (98) Revision of Titles 14.1 and 17 (Box 9, Folder 103)
- HB 1117 (98) Bonds for Northern VA Transportation District Program (Box 9, Folder 104)
- HB 1121 (98) Titles to Real or Leasehold Properties (Box 9, Folder 105)
- HB 1124 (98) Elected and Appointed School Board Officials (Box 9, Folder 106)
- HB 1126 (98) Income Tax: Contributions to Family and Children's Trust Fund (Box 9, Folder 107)
- HB 1128 (98) Sheriffs; Monthly Report to Compensation Board (Box 9, Folder 108)
- HB 1132 (98) Silvicultural Activities (Box 9, Folder 109)
- HB 1133 (98) Distribution Cost and Gas Road Improvement Tax for Water Projects (Box 10, Folder 1)
- HB 1135 (98) Coal Loading Facilities (Box 10, Folder 2)
- HB 1136 (98) Harold L. Ringley Bridge and Frank Clay Bridge (Box 10, Folder 3)
- HB 1138 (98) National Pollutant Discharge Elimination Permits; Penalties (Box 10, Folder 4)
- HB 1141 (98) Land Records Management (Box 10, Folder 5)
- HB 1144 (98) Exemplary Damages for Persons Injured by Intoxicated Drivers (Box 10, Folder 6)
- HB 1145 (98) Service of Garnishments on Corporations (Box 10, Folder 7)
- HB 1147 (98) Taxable Income of Residents (Box 10, Folder 8)
- HB 1148 (98) Cable Television; Use of Rights-of-Way (Box 10, Folder 9)
- HB 1149 (98) Employment; Solicitation and Sales (Box 10, Folder 10)
- HB 1153 (98) Animal Hospitals and Clinics (Box 10, Folder 11)
- HB 1155 (98) State Grievance Procedures; Award of Attorney's Fees (Box 10, Folder 12)
- HB 1168 (98) Speed Limits (Box 10, Folder 13)
- HB 1172 (98) Electric Utility Industry; Schedule (Box 10, Folder 14)
- HB 1174 (98) Charity Food Assistance Act (Box 10, Folder 15)
- HB 1175 (98) Mineral Mining (Box 10, Folder 16)
- HB 1190 (98) Correctional Enterprises; Sale of Prison Goods and Services (Box 10, Folder 17)
- HB 1191 (98) Bill of Rights Day (Box 10, Folder 18)
- HB 1195 (98) Sealing of Voting and Counting Equipment for Elections (Box 10, Folder 19)
- HB 1196 (98) Officers of Elections; Instruction on Use of Voting Equipment (Box 10, Folder 20)
- HB 1200 (98) Standards of Quality; Technological Proficiency (Box 10, Folder 21)
- HB 1202 (98) Health Ins. For State Employees; Mammograms (Box 10, Folder 22)
- HB 1203 (98) Comptroller; Recovery of Improper Payments to State Employees (Box 10, Folder 23)
- HB 1204 (98) Residential Property Disclosure Act (Box 10, Folder 24)
- HB 1209 (98) Potomac River Compact (Box 10, Folder 25)
- HB 1216 (98) Situs of Personal Property (Box 10, Folder 26)
- HB 1220 (98) Coalbed Methane Well Operations; Water Supply Replacement (Box 10, Folder 27)
- HB 1221 (98) Coalbed Methane Well Permits; Objections, Hearing (Box 10, Folder 28)
- HB 1222 (98) Coalbed Methane Wells; Drilling by a Cemetery (Box 10, Folder 29)
- HB 1223 (98) Gas and Oil Board (Box 10, Folder 30)
- HB 1228 (98) Pruning Certain Vegetation Within Highway Rights-of-Way (Box 10, Folder 31)
- HB 1232 (98) Special License Plates; FOP Associates and Auxiliary (Box 10, Folder 32)
- HB 1234 (98) Health Services Plans; Licenses Acupuncturists (Box 10, Folder 33)
- HB 1236 (98) Contracts; Procurement Act (Box 10, Folder 34)
- HB 1237 (98) Telecommunications Tower; Acquisition of Property (Box 10, Folder 35)
- HB 1240 (98) Contract Rental Vehicles for State Use (Box 10, Folder 36)
- HB 1242 (98) Broker's Liens (Box 10, Folder 37)
- HB 1244 (98) Definition of Coastal Primary Sand Dune (Box 10, Folder 38)
- HB 1245 (98) Real Estate Board; License Requirements (Box 10, Folder 39)
- HB 1246 (98) Real Estate Board; Protection of Escrow Funds (Box 10, Folder 40)
- HB 1247 (98) Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Abandoned Property (Box 10, Folder 41)
- HB 1253 (98) Fire Programs Fund (Box 10, Folder 42)
- HB 1254 (98) Labor and Employment; Exemptions from Child Labor Laws (Box 10, Folder 43)
- HB 1256 (98) Child Support (Box 10, Folder 44)
- HB 1264 (98) Marine Resources Commission; Membership (Box 10, Folder 45)
- HB 1265 (98) Consumer Real Estate Settlement Protection Act (Box 10, Folder 46)
- HB 1267 (98) Appeal Bond; Not Required for Certain Transportation Districts (Box 10, Folder 47)
- HB 1269 (98) Solicitation of Contributions; Definitions (Box 10, Folder 48)
- HB 1273 (98) Revised Uniform Limited Partnership Act (Box 10, Folder 49)
- HB 1276 (98) Racing Commission; Powers, Permits (Box 10, Folder 50)
- HB 1278 (98) Notification of Parents Regarding Pupil's Absence (Box 10, Folder 51)
- HB 1280 (98) Unemployment Compensation; Benefits Disqualification (Box 10, Folder 52)
- HB 1281 (98) Insurance; Pet Accident, Sickness and Hospitalization (Box 10, Folder 53)
- HB 1282 (98) Compensation of Court-Appointed Counsel (Box 10, Folder 54)
- HB 1286 (98) City Street Maintenance Payments (Box 10, Folder 55)
- HB 1287 (98) Teachers to Study Gifted Education (Box 10, Folder 56)
- HB 1288 (98) Gifted Education Pilot Program (Box 10, Folder 57)
- HB 1289 (98) Gifted Education Programs (Box 10, Folder 58)
- HB 1292 (98) Substance Abuse Services (Box 10, Folder 59)
- HB 1294 (98) Council on Coordinating Prevention (Box 10, Folder 60)
- HB 1295 (98) Boating; Reckless Operation of a Personal Watercraft (Box 10, Folder 61)
- HB 1297 (98) Eminent Domain; Condemnation by a Housing Authority (Box 10, Folder 62)
- HB 1298 (98) Community Development Authorities; Service Districts (Box 10, Folder 63)
- HB 1299 (98) Drug Control Act (Box 10, Folder 64)
- HB 1300 (98) Requirements for Controlled Substances Registration (Box 10, Folder 65)
- HB 1301 (98) Competition Council; Private Enterprise (Box 10, Folder 66)
- HB 1306 (98) Prisons and Corrections (Box 10, Folder 67)
- HB 1311 (98) Health Professions; Selling Eyeglasses (Box 10, Folder 68)
- HB 1312 (98) Property Transfer; Shenandoah Business Incubator and Technical Center (Box 10, Folder 69)
- HB 1314 (98) Naming of Public Buildings (Box 10, Folder 70)
- HB 1331 (98) Wireless Enhanced Public Safety Service Act (Box 10, Folder 71)
- HB 1335 (98) Hospital Authorities; Chesapeake and Norfolk (Box 10, Folder 72)
- HB 1336 (98) Criminal History Records Check; Community Services Boards (Box 10, Folder 75)
- HB 1338 (98) Real Estate Board; Approval of Continuing Education Courses (Box 10, Folder 74)
- HB 1339 (98) Commercial Vehicles and Commercial Vehicle Driver's Licenses (Box 10, Folder 75)
- HB 1340 (98) Educational Planning (Box 10, Folder 76)
- HB 1342 (98) Housing Development Authority; Powers (Box 10, Folder 77)
- HB 1343 (98) Student Expulsion and Searches (Box 10, Folder 78)
- HB 1344 (98) Commonwealth Character Initiative (Box 10, Folder 79)
- HB 1349 (98) Special License Plates; 400th Anniversary of Jamestown Settlement (Box 10, Folder 80)
- HB 1353 (98) Liability Insurance; Private Pleasure Watercraft (Box 10, Folder 81)
- HB 1354 (98) Small Claims Courts (Box 10, Folder 82)
- HB 1355 (98) Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Interest on Security Deposits (Box 10, Folder 83)
- HB 1356 (98) Property and Conveyances; Subdivided Land Sales Act (Box 10, Folder 84)
- HB 1357 (98) Real Estate Board; Filing of Annual Reports by Associations (Box 10, Folder 85)
- HB 1359 (98) Qualified Equity and Subordinated Debt Investments Tax Credit (Box 10, Folder 86)
- HB 1360 (98) Law Enforcement Personnel Training; Alzheimer's Disease (Box 10, Folder 87)
- HB 1364 (98) Department of General Services; Value Engineering (Box 10, Folder 88)
- HB 1367 (98) Landlord and Tenant; Prevention of Judgment of Forfeiture (Box 10, Folder 89)
- HB 1372 (98) Child Support Enforcement; Paternity (Box 10, Folder 90)
- HB 1373 (98) Child Support; Hearing for Obligee (Box 10, Folder 91)
- HB 1374 (98) Child Support Enforcement; New Hire Reporting Center (Box 10, Folder 92)
- HB 1375 (98) Domestic Relations; Support Orders (Box 11, Folder 1)
- HB 1376 (98) Administrative Orders for Support (Box 11, Folder 2)
- HB 1377 (98) State Case Registry of Child Support Records (Box 11, Folder 3)
- HB 1378 (98) Assisted Suicide (Box 11, Folder 4)
- HB 1380 (98) Age for Operation of a Motorboat; Penalty (Box 11, Folder 5)
- HB 1381 (98) Motorboat Safety Training (Box 11, Folder 6)
- HB 1386 (98) Child Care (Box 11, Folder 7)
- HB 1387 (98) Family Day Homes (Box 11, Folder 8)
- HB 1388 (98) Child Welfare Agencies (Box 11, Folder 9)
- HB 1390 (98) Condominium and Property Owners' Association Act (Box 11, Folder 10)
- HB 1391 (98) Hospitals; Inspections (Box 11, Folder 11)
- HB 1386 (98) Decisions of Zoning Administrator (Box 11, Folder 12)
- HB 1399 (98) Health Insurance for State Employees; Diabetes (Box 11, Folder 13)
- HB 1403 (98) Disposal of Exhibits (Box 11, Folder 14)
- HB 1405 (98) Industrial Development and Revenue Bond Act (Box 11, Folder 15)
- HB 1408 (98) Members of Regional Jail, etc. (Box 11, Folder 16)
- HB 1411 (98) Keeping of Ballots by Clerk (Box 11, Folder 17)
- HB 1413 (98) Health Insurance; Coverage for Early Intervention Services (Box 11, Folder 18)
- HB 1415 (98) Board for Contractors; Requirements for Licensure (Box 11, Folder 19)
- HB 1419 (98) Wetlands and Reparian Buffers; Taxation (Box 11, Folder 20)
- HB 1420 (98) Capital Murder (Box 11, Folder 21)
- HB 1423 (98) Transient Occupancy Tax; Dinwiddie County (Box 11, Folder 22)
- HB 1425 (98) Property Tax Exemption for Erosion Control Improvements (Box 11, Folder 23)
- HB 1426 (98) Speed Limits in Residential Districts (Box 11, Folder 24)
- HB 1427 (98) Frederick T. Gray Bridge (Box 11, Folder 25)
- HB 1430 (98) ABC; Enforcement of Sale of Tobacco to Minors (Box 11, Folder 27)
- 1998 Special Session (Box 11, Folder 29)
- 1998 Special Session: SB 4005 (98) Personal Property Tax Relief; School Construction (Box 11, Folder 30)
- 1998 Special Session: HB 4001 (98) Budget Bill (Box 11, Folder 31)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 1-58 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 59-164 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 165-278 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 279-394 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 395-488 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 573-650 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 651-716 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 717-772 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 773-789 Reconvened Session (Box 11, Folder 41)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 790-845 Reconvened Session (Box 11, Folder 42)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 846-872 Reconvened Session (Box 11, Folder 43)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 873-889 Reconvened Session (Box 11, Folder 44)
- 1998 Virginia Acts of Assembly: Chapters 890-908 Reconvened Session (Box 11, Folder 45)